staff.com 2019-10-06

# Privacy Policy - Staff.com

## Our Commitment To Data Security

Your privacy is imperative. Staff.com has developed this Privacy Statement to describe our practices of collecting and managing your information. We only collect and use your information through means allowed by law.

## Types Of Information Collected When Using The Staff.com Service

This Privacy Statement applies to all information collected or submitted on or through the Staff.com website or the desktop application.

Information collected while using the web application includes the following: Name, Email, Photo, Address, city, state, zip code or postal code. If paying for the service we will collect credit card numbers as it appears on the credit card. Credit card information is transmitted via SSL encryption and stored by our merchant account provider Stripe, Inc. Stripe is certified to “PCI Service Provider Level 1”. This is the most stringent level of certification available in the payments industry.

Additional information collected by the web and desktop application can include: the names of tasks to be worked on, the amount of time worked on tasks, time spent on breaks, time of starting work, time finishing work, names of applications used on your computer, websites visited, screenshots of your computer screen, project categories of tasks you visit. If you authorize we will record a 10 minute video of your desktop of you using the desktop application. We may record mouse movements of you using the web application in order to improve the usability of our site.

Screenshots recorded can be viewed by you and by any person who manages you in your company. You can delete screenshots from the system (and this will correspondingly delete the corresponding amount of time worked). All other information such as websites visited and applications used can be viewed by any person in your company who manages you and also by yourself. Screenshot, website and application data is only tracked when you record that you are working on your computer and is not recorded when you are on a break. Website and application monitoring is active for all users of the system when they are tracking time. Screenshot monitoring can be individually activated or deactivated by your company admin for team members on your team.

The Staff.com desktop app records the number of keystrokes or mouse movements you make. It does not however record where you click on the screen, and it does not record what you type. It is not a keystroke-logging application.

Other information recorded automatically includes: IP address where you logged in, browser type and browser software version.

## Using Your Information

We do not oblige you to provide us your personal information and you agree that you are providing it to Staff.com voluntarily. We may use your personal information to provide you with the services relating to the Staff.com platform. We will never rent or sell any personally identifiable information to a third party unless required to provide a service requested and agreed to by you via a signed Data Use Agreement. We reserve the right to disclose personal information as required by law.

Staff.com reserves the right to aggregate its user data and after removing all personally identifiable information, use it as test data to further enhance our software and/or improve its performance.

In addition, we track the usage of our website to learn which information is visited or read the most, and which pages are least visited. This helps Staff.com measure the effectiveness of its website and software.

Staff.com uses Amazon S3 storage for data, and Postmarkapp for email delivery.

Information is transmitted over 256-bit SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) with encryption. SSL is a security standard used around the world by bank and credit card websites, e-commerce sites, in fact, any site or company who demands the most secure forms of protected communication to keep people's personal and financial information safe.

Staff.com is committed to the security, privacy and integrity of your personal or company data.

## Correcting Your Information

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by logging into the website and editing your information.

## Cookies

Cookies are small text files sent through your browser and saved in your hard drive. Staff.com uses cookies to uniquely identify you and save the preferences you set from your previous visit into the site. You may choose to disable cookies by selecting this option on your browser. Disabling cookies may, however, disable some services activated using such technology.

## How Can We Further Help You?

For more questions about this privacy policy, please contact us.
